

# MUHAMMAD HASSAN

#### Web Designer | Frontend Developer

I am very experienced and working with clients in different time zones and locations, I am organized, adaptable, work well under pressure, learn quickly, keep to deadlines and am equally at ease working alone or as part of a team. I have Design over 500+ Home Pages, including projects for high profile clients like Dealer-e-Process and Alhokail.

#### Skills



# Contact

- ★ Lahore
- 03454104058

W3C Standards

- guru.frontend@gmail.com
- in muhammad-hassan-8771b616
- @mohhassanafzal
- f mohassansultan
- mohhassanafal48

## Experience

### Bilytica

#### Senior Frontend Developer | 2019 - Present

Design and Develop Interface of all Different products

- EMR software (Health)
- Tracking System (Track Employees and Order)
- · Point of Sale (Sale Purchase)
- · Payroll Software (Payroll and HRMS)
- · ERP Accounting System

#### Shifa4U

#### Frontend Engineer | 2018 - 2019

Work on project of American Tele Physicians (ATP), which is a physicians-led digital healthcare organization with vast experience in clinical informatics

- Smartclinix
- Shifa4U
- Online Doctor Portal

#### LiveAdmins | Dealer-e-Process

#### Web Developer/ Frontend Develope | 2016 - 2018

Design and Develop Interface of all Different Projects and Work Approximate 500+ Home pages of vehicles which are under Dealer-e-process.

- liveadmins
- · corporatehousingbyowner
- ukflightexperts
- .dealereprocess.com 500+
- 500 home page design in which, Top brands included like Kia, Nissan Toyota, Honda, BMW and much more.

## Some Important Key Achievements

### Achievements

- Knowledge of Web design with responsiveness.
- · Intermediate Knowledge of Backend Development
- Browser compatibility testing on: IE, Safari, Chrome, Firefox and mobile devices (phones/tablets).
- Worked with business and design requirements to develop web pages that adhered to company, industry and usability standards and more.
- · Promoting and communicating new ideas
- · Creating process improvements
- · Instituting new technologies
- · Writing maintainable cross-browser code
- Estimating time and costs for projects
- Ensuring code is scalable and responsive
- Convert old Design of project into latest Design
- Identifying innovative ideas and proof of concepts according to project requirements.

#### Education

#### Master Computer Science (Mcs)

Bahauddin Zakariya University, . | 2012 - 2014

CGPA - 3.1 / 4.0

Complete my master degree in 2012 with CGPA 3.1 out of 4. Complete Travelling system in my final year project.